Guide to Oversized Materials Flat.File.Cases
New York University Archives
Oversized Materials
circa 1735-2013
Flat.File.Cases
New York University Archives
8.0 Flat File Cases and 7 oversized boxes
Related Materials at the New York University Archives
Records of the Office of the University Architect, Joseph J. Roberto Collection (RG 11.4)
Washington Square Park (New York, NY) and Washington Square Area Image Collection, 1850-1990 (NYU.ARCH.PHOTO.00001)
General Note
This collection is oversized materials stored in 8 flat file cases and 7 oversized boxes stored on top of flat file 6. Cases 1-5 and 7 and 8 are in the front reading room and case 6 is in the rear of the Archives. All contents are described in the finding aid except Series VIII: posters and event fliers which are described in an Access database on the University Archives shared drive and cannot be accessed remotely.
Architecture.; Greenwich Village (New York, N.Y.); Historic buildings |z New York (State) |z New York.; New York University |x Buildings.; New York University. University Heights Campus.; New York University. Washington Square Campus.; Washington Square Park (New York, N.Y.)
- Series I: Washington Square Area and Buildings
  Greenwich Village (New York, N.Y.); New York University |x Buildings.; New York University. University Heights Campus.; New York University. Washington Square Campus.; Washington Square Park (New York, N.Y.)
  - Subseries A: Buildings
    - Block Plan: Block 546 (West 4th Street and Mercer Street), 1964 September 22 (Map-case 6, Drawer 11)
    - Campus Maps, Greenwich Village Maps, Site Plans, undated (Map-case 3, Drawer 4)
    - Campus Overview: Philip Johnson Building Plans for Washington Square East, South, undated (Map-case 2, Drawer 14)
    - Campus Overviews: Artist Renderings [2], undated (Map-case 2, Drawer 15)
    - Unidentified Building: Artist Renderings (Eggers and Higgins, Architects), undated (Map-case 2, Drawer 14)
    - Unidentified Building: Artist Renderings (Walter C. Pfeiffer, Architect), undated (Map-case 2, Drawer 14)
    - Unidentified Red Sandstone Building: Artist Renderings, undated (Map-case 2, Drawer 15)
    - Unnamed Buildings: Engineering Plans, undated (Map-case 2, Drawer 11)
    - Unnamed Buildings: Plans: Bursar's Office, undated (Map-case 2, Drawer 11)
    - Unnamed Buildings: Plans: Council Room, undated (Map-case 2, Drawer 11)
    - Unnamed Buildings: Plans: Recorder's Office, undated (Map-case 2, Drawer 11)
    - Unnamed Buildings: Plans: Theater, undated (Map-case 2, Drawer 11)
    - Unnamed Buildings: Plans: Theater and Media Building, undated (Map-case 2, Drawer 11)
    - 1 5th Avenue (Suite 18-G): Architectural Plans, circa 1960s-1970s (Map-case 2, Drawer 3)
    - 2 5th Avenue (Residences): Architectural Plans, circa 1960s (Map-case 2, Drawer 3)
    - 85 West 3rd Street: Floor Plans (2), 1975 September 16-October 9 (Map-case 6, Drawer 11)
    - 89 West 3rd Street: Architectural Plans, 1970 August 5 (Map-case 2, Drawer 4)
    - 102 West 3rd Street: Architectural Plans, 1968-1970 (Map-case 2, Drawer 4)
    - 15-19 West 4th Street, undated (Map-case 3, Drawer 6)
    - 510 West Broadway (144-146 Bleecker Street): Architectural Plans, 1966 March 22, 28 (Map-case 2, Drawer 4)
    - 684 Broadway: Architectural Plans, 1900s (Map-case 2, Drawer 4)
      Separated Materials
      Original Location: Records of the Office of the Treasurer (Muriel L. Mantel) (RG 10.9)
    - 693 Broadway: Architectural Plans, 1899, 1965 (Map-case 2, Drawer 4)
      Original Location: Records of the Office of the University Architect, Joseph J. Roberto Collection (RG 11.4)
    - 715 Broadway (1 Washington Place): Architectural Plans, undated (Map-case 2, Drawer 2)
    - 285 Mercer Street, undated (Map-case 4, Drawer 14)
    - University Place and 8th Street (Proposed): Architectural Plans, 1900s (Map-case 2, Drawer 3)
    - 1 University Place (Residences and Commercial Space): Architectural Plans, 1900s (Map-case 2, Drawer 3)
    - 13-19 University Place, undated (Map-case 3, Drawer 8)
    - 14 Washington Mews: Architectural Plans, 1966-1981 (Map-case 2, Drawer 3)
    - 3-5 Washington Place: Blueprints, 1971 (Map-case 2, Drawer 1)
    - 3-5 Washington Place: Renovation Blueprints, 1979 (Map-case 5, Drawer 6)
    - 10 Washington Place: Architectural Plans, 1967-1986 (Map-case 2, Drawer 2)
    - 21 Washington Place: Architectural Plans, Artist Renderings, Proposed Site Uses, 1964, 1978, 1984 (Map-case 2, Drawer 2)
    - 21 Washington Place: Alterations, Floor Plans, Aug 3, 1976 (Map-case 5, Drawer 6)
    - 23-29 Washington Place: Architectural Plans, undated (Map-case 2, Drawer 2)
    - 1-6 Washington Square North, undated (Map-case 3, Drawer 5)
    - 7-13 Washington Square North: Architectural Plans, 1939 (Map-case 2, Drawer 3)
    - 14 Washington Square North (Residences): Architectural Plans, circa 1960s (Map-case 2, Drawer 3)
    - 37 Washington Square North: Blueprints, Floor Plans by Robert Turner, Interior Views, undated (Map-case 5, Drawer 6)
    - 51 Washington Square South: Floor Plans, 1946 July (Map-case 6, Drawer 11)
    - 29 Washington Square West, undated (Map-case 2, Drawer 5)
    - 37 Washington Square West, undated (Map-case 2, Drawer 5)
    - 10 Waverly Place, undated (Map-case 4, Drawer 14)
    - 16 Waverly Place ("Upstairs at Harout's"): Architectural Plans for Library, 1900s (Map-case 2, Drawer 3)
    - 28-30 Waverly Place: Drawing Extension, undated (Map-case 5, Drawer 15)
    - 170 Waverly Place: Blueprints, Floor Plans by H.T. Graves [Assoc.], Interior Sketches, Apr 16, 1974 (Map-case 5, Drawer 6)
    - 249 Greene Street color drawing, 1960s (Map-case 6, Drawer 6)
    - West Broadway: Studies, undated (Map-case 2, Drawer 5)
    - 528-30 West Broadway (at Bleecker Street): Architectural Plans, 1962 (Map-case 2, Drawer 4)
    - Andre and Bella Meyer Physics Building (707 Broadway; 2-4 Washington Place; 4-6 Washington Place): Architectural Plans, 1962-1965 (Map-case 2, Drawer 1)
    - Andre and Bella Meyer Physics Building (707 Broadway; 2-4 Washington Place; 4-6 Washington Place): Architectural Plans, 1965 (Map-case 2, Drawer 1)
    - Andre and Bella Meyer Physics Building (707 Broadway; 2-4 Washington Place; 4-6 Washington Place): Architectural Plans, 1962-1963 (Map-case 2, Drawer 1)
    - Andre and Bella Meyer Physics Building (707 Broadway; 2-4 Washington Place; 4-6 Washington Place): Architectural Plans, 1965-1966 (Map-case 2, Drawer 1)
    - Andre and Bella Meyer Physics Building (707 Broadway; 2-4 Washington Place; 4-6 Washington Place): Architectural Plans, 1962-1966 (Map-case 2, Drawer 1)
    - Biology Department Center (721-727 Broadway): Architectural Plans, 1978 (Map-case 2, Drawer 3)
    - Brittany House; Hotel Brittany (55 East 10th Street): Architectural Plans, 1966 (Map-case 2, Drawer 3)
    - Brittany House; Hotel Brittany (55 East 10th Street): Architectural Plans, Sep 29, 1975 (Map-case 5, Drawer 6)
    - Broadway Central Hotel (673 Broadway): Architectural Plans, 1960-1962 (Map-case 2, Drawer 4)
    - Brown Building, undated (Map-case 3, Drawer 5)
    - Center for Jewish Culture, Proposed (West Broadway and West 3rd Street): Architectural Plans, 1963 November-1964 June (Map-case 2, Drawer 4)
    - Chancellor's Residence (34 West 11th Street): Architectural Plans, 1967 (Map-case 2, Drawer 3)
    - Coles Sports and Recreation Center, undated (Map-case 2, Drawer 20)
    - Coles Sports and Recreation Center: Sketches, undated (Map-case 5, Drawer 6)
    - Commerce Building and Shimkin Hall, undated (Map-case 2, Drawer 10)
    - Computing Facility: Architectural Plans, 1975 (Map-case 2, Drawer 3)
    - Conservation Center (14 East 78th Street), undated (Map-case 3, Drawer 6)
    - Deans' Apartment: Floor Plans, undated (Map-case 2, Drawer 11)
    - Deutsches Haus (Department of Germanic Languages and Literature), undated (Map-case 4, Drawer 3)
    - Dormitory (University Place and 8th Street): Artist Renderings, 1960 (Map-case 2, Drawer 13)
    - Dreyfus Hall of Science: Artist Renderings (Eggers and Higgins, Architects), 1949 (Map-case 2, Drawer 15)
    - Dreyfus Hall of Science: Artist Renderings (Walter C. Pfeiffer, Architect), undated (Map-case 2, Drawer 14)
    - East Building (239 Greene Street), undated (Map-case 2, Drawer 9)
    - Education Building (35-41 West 4th Street and Greene Street), undated (Map-case 2, Drawer 9, Map-case 3, Drawer 6)
    - Faculty Club (22 Washington Square North): Architectural Plans, 1963, 1969 (Map-case 2, Drawer 3)
    - Founders' Monument: Artist Renderings, undated (Map-case 1, Drawer 3)
    - Furman Hall (Law School), undated (Map-case 4, Drawer 3)
    - Goddard Hall, South Building (80 Washington Square East), Stern Residence Hall, Students Building (51 West 4th Street): Plan Compilations, undated (Map-case 3, Drawer 10)
    - Goddard Hall, South Building (80 Washington Square East), Stern Residence Hall, Students Building (51 West 4th Street): Basement, Cellar, undated (Map-case 3, Drawer 10)
    - Goddard Hall, South Building (80 Washington Square East), Stern Residence Hall, Students Building (51 West 4th Street): Floor 1, undated (Map-case 3, Drawer 10)
    - Goddard Hall, South Building (80 Washington Square East), Stern Residence Hall, Students Building (51 West 4th Street): Floors 2-7, Roof, undated (Map-case 3, Drawer 10)
    - Goddard Hall, Stern Residence Hall, undated (Map-case 3, Drawer 9, Map-case 4, Drawer 11)
    - Gould Dormitory, undated (Map-case 4, Drawer 12)
    - Graduate Student Residence Hall (26th Street and 1st Avenue), undated (Map-case 3, Drawer 13)
    - Hayden Hall (33 Washington Square West), undated (Map-case 3, Drawer 6, Map-case 2, Drawer 5)
    - Hayden Hall and Vanderbilt Hall: Artist Renderings (Eggers and Higgins, Architects), circa 1947-1952 (Box 1)
    - Judson Hall, undated (Map-case 3, Drawer 1)
    - Judson Memorial Church, undated (Map-case 2, Drawer 5)
    - Kevorkian Center (50 Washington Square South): Architectural Plans, 1967-1978 (Map-case 2, Drawer 4)
    - Kevorkian Center (50 Washington Square South): Artist Rendering, undated (Box 2)
      Separated Materials Note
    - Kevorkian Center: Artists rendering, 1960s (Map-case 10, Drawer 10)
    - Kimball Hall (22 Waverly Place; 246 Greene Street): Architectural Plans, 1962 (Map-case 2, Drawer 3)
    - Kimmel Center: Fabric Swatch Board, undated (Map-case 4, Drawer 2)
    - Kimmel Center: Plans, undated (Map-case 4, Drawer 1)
    - Law Center (Law Library, Vanderbilt Hall), undated (Map-case 3, Drawer 13)
    - Leonard Stern Student Residence Hall (Later Goddard Hall), undated (Map-case 4, Drawer 11)
    - Loeb Student Center, undated (Map-case 3, Drawer 11)
    - Main Building/Main Block, undated (Map-case 3, Drawer 5)
    - Main Building: Artist Renderings, undated (Map-case 2, Drawer 14)
    - La Maison Francaise (15-16 Washington Mews): Architectural Plans, 1978 February 13 (Map-case 2, Drawer 4)
    - La Maison Francaise (15-16 Washington Mews): Artist Rendering, undated (Map-case 1, Drawer 3)
    - Loeb Student Center: NYU Photo Bureau Prints (6), 1963 and 1970 (Box 1)
    - Main Building: Exterior Photograph of Entrance, circa 1980s (Map-case 5, Drawer 16)
    - Main Building: Photographs (2), undated (Map-case 5, Drawer 16)
    - Musical Theatre Hall of Fame, undated (Map-case 4, Drawer 14)
    - Nichols Hall: Artist Renderings, undated (Map-case 2, Drawer 15)
    - NYU Bookstore (24-26 Washington Place): Remodeling Plan, 1947 (Map-case 2, Drawer 2)
    - NYU Cafe and Violet Cafe (80 Washington Square East and 51 West 4th Street), undated (Map-case 3, Drawer 9)
    - NYU Mitchell-Lama Apartments and Washington Square Apartments: Site Development Costs, circa 1940s-1960s (Map-case 6, Drawer 11)
    - NYU Redesign: Artist Renderings (Walter C. Pfeiffer, Architect), undated (Map-case 2, Drawer 14)
    - NYU Washington Square Center, undated (Map-case 3, Drawer 8)
    - Palladium Site: Furniture Layout, undated (Map-case 4, Drawer 5)
    - Physical Science Building, undated (Map-case 4, Drawer 14)
    - Press Annex Building (24-26 Washington Place): Architectural Plans, undated, 1964 (Map-case 2, Drawer 2)
    - Proposed Class Room Building [East of Commerce]: Architectural Study, circa 1959 (Box 2)
    - Proposed: Education Buildings (Including proposal for new library), undated (Map-case 4, Drawer 4, Map-case 2, Drawer 9)
    - Proposed: Farkas Hall (Schools of Education and Social Work) at Washington Square East, Washington Place, West 4th Street, undated (Map-case 4, Drawer 5)
    - Proposed: General University Library: Artist Renderings (Warner, Burns, Toan, Lunde, Architects), 1962 (Map-case 2, Drawer 14)
    - Proposed: New Library (Warner, Burns, Toan, Lunde, Architects), 1963 (Map-case 3, Drawer 15)
    - Proposed: Puerto Rican Cultural Center, undated (Map-case 2, Drawer 11)
    - Proposed: Renovations for Old University Building (Not Implemented; McKim, Mead and White), undated (Map-case 3, Drawer 4)
    - Proposed: Sports Center, undated (Map-case 2, Drawer 20)
    - Reading Consortium (87 West 3rd Street): Demolition and Architectural Plan, 1976 January 26-April 16 (Map-case 6, Drawer 11)
    - Renaissance House (160 Bleecker Street): Architectural Plans and Brochure, 1947, 1961 (Map-case 2, Drawer 4)
    - Research Library: Artist Renderings, 1952 (Map-case 2, Drawer 15)
    - Research Library: Artist Renderings (Eggers and Higgins, Architects), 1952 (Map-case 2, Drawer 15)
    - Research Library: Artist Renderings (Walter C. Pfeiffer, Architect), undated (Map-case 2, Drawer 14)
    - Residence Hall: Artist Renderings, undated (Map-case 2, Drawer 13)
    - Rubin Residence Hall: Demolition Plans, Floor Plans, Sketches of 2nd Floor, May 26, 1969 (Map-case 5, Drawer 6)
    - School of Education: Artist Renderings (Perkins and Will, Architects), undated (Map-case 2, Drawer 15)
    - Silver Towers (University Plaza, University Village), undated (Map-case 3, Drawer 8)
    - South Building, undated (Map-case 2, Drawer 9)
    - South Building, Students Building: Exterior and Interior Sketches and Views, undated (Map-case 3, Drawer 9)
    - South Building, Students Building: Interior Components, Details, Systems, undated (Map-case 3, Drawer 9)
    - South Building, Students Building: Interior Section Floor Plans, undated (Map-case 3, Drawer 9)
    - South Building, Students Building: Sectional and Elevation Views, undated (Map-case 3, Drawer 9)
    - Student Center (West Broadway and West 3rd Street): Architectural Plans, 1954 March 4 (Map-case 2, Drawer 4)
    - Student Center: Artist Renderings, undated (Map-case 2, Drawer 14)
    - Students Building (80 Washington Square East), undated (Map-case 2, Drawer 9)
    - Students Building (80 Washington Square East): Floor Plans, 1963 June 13 (Map-case 6, Drawer 11)
    - Tisch Hall and Gould Plaza, undated (Map-case 3, Drawer 6)
    - Drawing of Tisch Hall, 1960s (Map-case 5, Drawer 10)
    - Tisch School of the Arts, undated (Map-case 3, Drawer 6)
    - University Building: Renovation Plans (McKim, Mead, and White), 1893 (Map-case 3, Drawer 4)
    - University Prep School, Proposed New Building for (Mercer Street and West 4th Street): Architectural Plans, 1965-1966 (Map-case 2, Drawer 4)
    - Warren Weaver Hall, undated (Map-case 4, Drawer 5)
    - Washington Place East Building (18-24 Washington Place): Architectural Plans, undated, 1963 (Map-case 2, Drawer 2)
    - Washington Square Aerial Photos: Photo Bureau Prints (2), 1971 (Box 1)
    - Washington Square Area Maps, undated (Map-case 3, Drawer 4)
    - Washington Square Area Maps: Insurance, undated (Map-case 3, Drawer 13)
    - Washington Square Center Map, 1967 September (Map-case 5, Drawer 11)
    - Washington Square Center (School of Education Students Building and South Building): Architectural Plans, undated (Map-case 1, Drawer 1)
    - Washington Square East: Building Images, undated (Box 1)
    - Washington Square Park: Aerial Photograph, undated (Map-case 5, Drawer 16)
    - Washington Square Park: Aerial View (Walter C. Pfeiffer, Architect), undated (Map-case 2, Drawer 14)
    - Washington Square Park: Map, 1960 (Map-case 5, Drawer 16)
    - Washington Square Park: Plans for Commencement, 1987 (Map-case 5, Drawer 10)
    - Washington Square Park: Renovation Plans (copies), 1939 (Map-case 2, Drawer 1)
    - Washington Square Park: Topographical Survey, undated (Map-case 3, Drawer 4)
    - Washington Square South: Artist Renderings, undated (Box 2)
    - Washington Square Southeast: Proposal of New York University Relating to Washington Square Southeast Project, 1960 January (Box 2)
      Original Location: Records of the Office of the University Architect, Joseph J. Roberto Collection (RG 11.4), Box 18, Folder 36.
    - Washington Square Village, undated (Map-case 3, Drawer 6)
    - Waverly Building, undated (Map-case 2, Drawer 10)
    - Weinstein Residence Hall (5-11 University Place), undated (Map-case 3, Drawer 7)
    - Weinstein Residence Hall (5-11 University Place): Artist Renderings, undated (Map-case 2, Drawer 13)
  - Subseries B: Elmer Holmes Bobst Library
    - Bobst Library Development Plans Book, circa 1950s-1960s (Map-case 1, Drawer 5)
    - Exterior: Artist Rendering (1 of 2), circa 1950s-1960s (Box 2)
    - Exterior: Artist Rendering (2 of 2) (Box 2)
    - Interiors: Artist Renderings (4), undated, 1966 (Map-case 2, Drawer 19)
    - Alpine Sheet Metal Drawings, undated (Map-case 3, Drawer 20)
    - First Annual Bobst Literary Award Banquet: Front Elevation, circa 1983 (Map-case 6, Drawer 11)
    - First Annual Bobst Literary Award Banquet: Main Floor Plan, 1983 October 26 (Map-case 6, Drawer 11)
    - Floor Plans, 1974 (Map-case 5, Drawer 10)
    - Frontal and Sectional Views, undated (Map-case 3, Drawer 15)
    - Master Plans Compilation, undated (Map-case 3, Drawer 15)
    - Master Plans Compilation (Johnson and Foster), undated (Map-case 3, Drawer 16)
    - Philip Johnson Plan Compilations, undated (Map-case 3, Drawer 15)
    - Photographs: Interior, undated (Map-case 2, Drawer 15)
    - Site Studies, Zoning, undated (Map-case 3, Drawer 15)
    - Unspecified Floor, undated (Map-case 3, Drawer 19)
    - A Level (Subcellar), undated (Map-case 3, Drawer 16)
    - A Level (Subcellar), 1979 Renovations, undated (Map-case 3, Drawer 16)
    - B Level (Cellar), undated (Map-case 3, Drawer 16)
    - First Floor, undated (Map-case 3, Drawer 17)
    - Mezzanine, undated (Map-case 3, Drawer 17)
    - 2nd Floor, undated (Map-case 3, Drawer 17)
    - 2nd Floor: Avery Fisher Center, undated (Map-case 3, Drawer 17)
    - 3rd-12th Floor (12th Floor Furniture Layout, President's Office), undated (Map-case 3, Drawer 18)
    - Book Conveyor and Pneumatic Tube Systems, undated (Map-case 3, Drawer 20)
    - Bookstacks, undated (Map-case 3, Drawer 20)
    - Card Catalog, undated (Map-case 3, Drawer 20)
    - Carrels, undated (Map-case 3, Drawer 20)
    - Duct, Electrical, Lighting, and Telephone Systems, undated (Map-case 3, Drawer 20)
    - Faculty Study Areas, undated (Map-case 3, Drawer 20)
    - First Floor Control Counters, undated (Map-case 3, Drawer 20)
    - Lounges, undated (Map-case 3, Drawer 19)
    - Mail Room and Shipping, undated (Map-case 3, Drawer 19)
    - Multi-Media Center, undated (Map-case 3, Drawer 19)
    - Reserve Reading Room (Floor not specified), undated (Map-case 3, Drawer 16)
    - Roof Plan, undated (Map-case 3, Drawer 19)
    - Staff Work Areas, undated (Map-case 3, Drawer 19)
    - Tables, undated (Map-case 3, Drawer 20)
- Series II: University Heights Area and Buildings
  - Subseries A: Buildings
    - University Heights Campus, East 25th Street: Aerial Photos, circa 1900s (Box 1)
    - Campus Map and Aerial Photo, 1937 (Map-case 2, Drawer 6)
    - Central Campus Overview (With new buildings): Artist Renderings, undated (Map-case 2, Drawer 12)
    - Armory, undated (Map-case 2, Drawer 6)
    - Alumni Gymnasium, undated (Map-case 2, Drawer 6)
    - Bliss Building, undated (Map-case 2, Drawer 6)
    - Faculty Club, undated (Map-case 2, Drawer 6)
    - Four-Building Complex: Artist Renderings, undated (Map-case 2, Drawer 12)
    - Gould Memorial Library (McKim, Mead and White, Architects), undated (Map-case 3, Drawer 1)
    - Gould Memorial Library: Alteration Plans, 1950s-1960s (Map-case 3, Drawer 1)
    - Gould Student Center, undated (Map-case 2, Drawer 6)
    - Guggenheim School of Aeronautics, undated (Map-case 3, Drawer 2)
    - Hall of Fame, undated (Map-case 3, Drawer 2)
    - Hall of Fame: Blueprints, Aug 15, 1924 (Map-case 5, Drawer 8)
    - Havemeyer Laboratory and Annex, undated (Map-case 2, Drawer 7)
    - Language Hall (McKim, Mead, and White, Architects), 1950s-1960s (Map-case 3, Drawer 1)
    - Loew Dormitory, undated (Map-case 2, Drawer 7)
    - Loring Place, 1970 (Map-case 2, Drawer 7)
    - MacCracken Hall, undated (Map-case 2, Drawer 7)
    - Marcel Breuer Building Views: Artist Renderings, undated (Map-case 2, Drawer 12)
    - Marcel Breuer Comprehensive campus plan Section I, 1963 (Map-case 6, Drawer 10)
    - Marcel Breuer Comprehensive campus plan Section II, 1963 (Map-case 6, Drawer 10)
    - Natural Science Hall, undated (Map-case 2, Drawer 7)
    - Nichols Chemistry Building, undated (Map-case 2, Drawer 7)
    - Philosophy Hall, undated (Map-case 2, Drawer 7)
    - Plaza Near Gould Library: Artist Renderings, undated (Map-case 2, Drawer 12)
    - Religious Center, undated (Map-case 2, Drawer 8)
    - Residence Hall, 1958 (Map-case 3, Drawer 2)
    - Sage Engineering Building and Annex, undated (Map-case 2, Drawer 8)
    - Science Library, undated (Map-case 2, Drawer 8)
    - Sedgewick Avenue Dormitory, undated (Map-case 2, Drawer 8)
    - South Hall, undated (Map-case 2, Drawer 8)
    - Tech II Engineering Building, undated (Map-case 3, Drawer 2)
    - Technology II Building (See also Marcel Breuer Plans Book), undated (Map-case 2, Drawer 8)
    - Various Buildings: Altschul House, undated (Map-case 2, Drawer 6)
    - Various Buildings: Begrisch Hall, undated (Map-case 2, Drawer 6)
    - Various Buildings: Butler Hall, undated (Map-case 2, Drawer 6)
    - Various Buildings: Dormitory, 1965 (Map-case 2, Drawer 6)
    - Various Buildings: Proposed: Dormitory, 1966 (Map-case 2, Drawer 6)
    - Various Buildings: Green Building, undated (Map-case 2, Drawer 6)
    - Various Buildings: Mechanical and Engineering Design Lab, undated (Map-case 2, Drawer 6)
    - Various Buildings: Old Engineering Building, undated (Map-case 2, Drawer 6)
    - Various Buildings: West Hall, undated (Map-case 2, Drawer 6)
    - Watercolor Sketch of Campus, 1960s (Map-case 5, Drawer 8)
  - Subseries B: Development and Planning
    - University Heights Development Plans Book (Marcel Breuer and Associates Architects), 1963 (Map-case 1, Drawer 5)
    - University Heights Dormitory Plans Book (Marcel Breuer and Associates Architects), 1958 January (Map-case 1, Drawer 5)
    - Blueprints, Aug 15, 1924 (Map-case 5, Drawer 8)
    - Campus Maps and Plans, Property Maps, undated (Map-case 3, Drawer 2)
    - Entrances, Parking, Roadways, undated (Map-case 3, Drawer 2)
    - Floor Plans: Exterior, Sectional Views, undated (Map-case 3, Drawer 1)
    - Floor Plans: Structural Detail Plans, undated (Map-case 3, Drawer 1)
    - Group Living Plans, undated (Map-case 3, Drawer 2)
    - Landscaping Plans, undated (Map-case 3, Drawer 2)
    - New Library Plans, undated (Map-case 3, Drawer 2)
    - NYU University Heights Center Map, undated (Map-case 3, Drawer 2)
    - Sketch of Apartments, undated (Map-case 5, Drawer 8)
- Series III: Other University Buildings
  - 1071 6th Avenue (at 41st Street), undated (Map-case 2, Drawer 20)
  - Administration Building and Housing (Sterling Forest, Manhattan, New York, NY), undated (Map-case 2, Drawer 20)
  - Bellevue Medical Center: Blueprints and Plans, circa 1956-1962 (Map-case 5, Drawer 6)